片名:穆赫兰道
你在干吗?  我们不该在这停呀
What are you doing? We don't stop here.
下车
Get out of the car.
那些家伙在车后找到的
The boys found this on the floor, in the back of the Caddy.
恩  我看过了
Yeah, they showed me.
可能和案子没关系
Could be unrelated.
可能吧
Could be.
死者中有戴珍珠项链的吗?
Any of those dead kids wearing pearl earrings?
没有
No.
可能是其他人落下的
Could be someone's missing, maybe.
我也是这么想
That what I'm thinking.
就剩一个包了
Just one more bag after that.
维奇斯餐馆 (日落大道)
我只想来这
I just wanted to come here.
来维奇斯餐馆?
To Winkie's?
只是这间
This Winkie's.
为什么偏认准这间?
Okay. Why this Winkie's?
有点难以启齿
It's kind of embarrassing.
说吧
Go ahead.
我做了个与此地有关的梦 是吗?
I had a dream about this place. Oh, boy.
明白我的意思吗?
See what I mean?
是的 你做了个与此地有关的梦
Okay, so you had a dream about this place.
然后呢
Tell me.
我是第二次做这个梦了 两次都是一样的
it's the second one I've had. But they're both the same.
梦的开始是我来到这儿...
They start out that I'm in here but...
当时既不是白天也不是晚上...
it's not day or night...
半黑半白的  明白吗?
it's kind of half-night, you know?
除了这些灯光外
But it looks just like this.
周围环境就像现在这样
Except for the light.
我说不出来的害怕...
And I'm scared like I can't tell you. Of all people...
你就站在那边
you're standing right over there.
站在柜台旁
By that counter.
两次梦里都有你   而且你都是一副受惊吓的样子
You're in both dreams and you're scared.
看到你吓成那样  我更害怕...
I get even more frightened when I see how afraid you are, and...
然后我意识到是怎么回事了
then I realize what it is.
有一个男人...
There's a man...
在这个地方后面
in back of this place
就是被他吓的
He's the one who's doing it.
我可以透过墙看见他
I can see him through the wall.
我可以看见他的脸
I can see his face.
我希望永远不会在现实中看见那张脸
I hope that I never see that face ever outside of the dream.
就是这样了
That's it.
所以...你来这看他是否存在
So...you came to see if he's out there.
为了消除这种恐惧感
To get rid of this god-awful feeling.
好的
Right then.
他就在这附近
It's around the back.
丹  你没事吧
Dan! Dan, are you all right?
还是没找到那女孩
The girl is still missing.
说吧
Talk to me.
没什么变化
The same.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
该说再见了  贝蒂
Well, it's time to say good-bye, Betty.
-旅途中有你做伴真不错  -谢谢
-It's been so nice traveling with you. -Thank you, Irene.
我好兴奋好紧张  和你聊天真的很开心
I was so excited and nervous. It was sure great to have you to talk to.
-记住  我要在大荧幕上看到你  -好的
-I'll watch for you on the big screen. -Okay, Irene.
会有那么一天吗
Won't that be the day?
祝你好运  亲爱的贝蒂
Good luck, Betty dear.
-保重  -我会的
-Take care of yourself and be careful. -I will.
谢谢你  亲爱的
Thanks, again.
贝蒂  很高兴见到你  祝你好运
Betty, it was so nice meeting you. All the luck in the world.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的包呢?
My bags?
要去哪?
Where to?
哈文赫特1612号
1612, Hayvenhurst.
知道
Got it.
我打赌你就是贝蒂
Ten bucks says you're Betty.
是的
Yes.
-你是莲露莉斯夫人吧?  -是的  宝贝
-It is Mrs. Lenoix, isn't it? -In all my living glory, baby.
很高兴见到你 叫我可可就行了  别人都这么叫我
Pleased to meet you. Call me Coco. Everybody else does.
-在这等等  我要去拿钥匙  -好的 可可
-Wait there and I'll go get the key. -Okay, Coco.
维金斯
Wilkins!
如果那该死的狗再在大院里拉屎的话...
If that damn dog craps in the courtyard one more time...
-我就把它烤来做早餐 -你没养宠物吧
-I'm just gonna bank his little butt for breakfast! -You don't have any pets?
没有  虽然是合法的
No, I don't. They're allowed.
但我真的不喜欢这儿有宠物
I just don't like them in here for obvious reasons.
这儿曾经住过一个男人
There was a man that lived here once that
他养了一只袋鼠
had a prizefighting kangaroo.
你想象不到那只袋鼠 在这院子里做了些什么
You just wouldn't believe what that kangaroo did to this courtyard.
一起去看看你姨妈的房子吧  挺不错的
Let's go see your aunt's apartment. It's a good one.
我等不及了
I can hardly wait.
真难以置信! 我告诉过你
It's unbelievable! I told you.
你姨妈事先应该交待清楚了  这是钥匙
You and your aunt probably have an understanding, so here's the key.
需要什么尽管跟我说
And if you need anything, just give a holler.
这儿的人和我关系很好
Everybody in this building is pretty much okay with me...
否则他们也不会住这了
or they wouldn't be here.
如果你愿意  迟点会介绍你们认识
If you like, later on I'll introduce you around.
如果不愿意的话也别勉强
Well, no hard feelings if you don't.
对不起  露茜姨妈没说过这还有人
I'm sorry. My aunt Ruth didn't tell me someone was gonna be here.
-很对不起  -没关系
-I'm so sorry. -It's okay.
我是露茜的侄女 我叫贝蒂 她应该说过我会来吧?
I'm Ruth's niece. My name is Betty. I'm sure she told you I was coming.
出了点意外  我才在这的
There was an accident. I came here.
我明白  我看到衣服了
I understand. I saw the dress.
对不起  你没事吧?
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
发生什么事了?
What happened?
一起车...
A car...
车祸
a car accident.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
没事
I think so.
我只是...
I was just...
在洗澡
taking a shower.
不好意思 你继续洗吧
Oh, my God, I'm sorry. I'll let you get back to that.
我去整理行李
I'm gonna get unpacked.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
不好意思  我还是出去吧  稍后再谈
I'm sorry, I'll get out of here. We can talk later.
我叫...
My name is...
丽塔
Rita.
你是我姨妈的同事吗?
Do you work with my aunt?
不  我...不好意思
No, I...I'm sorry...
是我多事了
it's none of my business.
她那头红发真漂亮
She has pretty red hair.
她正在加拿大拍电影
She's letting me stay here while she's working on a movie...
叫我来这住  估计你都知道的吧
that's being made in Canada, but I guess you already know that.
我一辈子也买不起这种地方
I couldn't afford a place like this in a million years.
除非我能成为电影明星
Unless, of course, I'm discovered and become a movie star.
当然  我更愿意做个演技派  而不是靠脸蛋
Of course, I'd rather be known as a great actress than a movie star...
不过有些人是两者兼备的
but sometimes people end up being both. So...
这就是我来这儿的目的
that is, I guess you'd say, the story of why I came here.
不好意思  我太兴奋了
I'm sorry. I'm just so excited to be here.
我刚从安大略湖的深河镇来 现在我终于来到这个...
I just came here from Deep River, Ontario, and now I'm in this...
梦一般的地方  能体会我的感受吗?
dream place! Well, you can imagine how I feel.
坐下吧
Sit down.
你哪里受伤了?
Where were you hurt?
-我们得叫个医生来 -不要
-We should call a doctor. -No.
-可能挺严重的 -不  我想睡觉
-But this could be serious. -No, I need to sleep.
如果是脑震荡  你不能睡觉的
If you have a concussion, you shouldn't sleep.
我睡会就没事了
I'll be okay if I sleep.
我只想躺下睡觉
I just need to lie down here and sleep.
亚当  我们想提些建议...
You see, Adam, there are some suggestions that ought to be brought forward.
你说过愿意接受意见的
And I know you said you would entertain suggestions.
大家都希望你能这么做
And that's all anybody here is asking you to do.
你在说什么? 思路要开放一些
What are you talking about? An open mind.
你在重新挑选女主角  因此我们...
You're in the process of recasting your lead actress, and I'm...
我们希望你思路能开放一些
we are asking you to keep an open mind.
上次的是什么?
What was it the last time?
好的  试试下一位  他不会喜欢的
Okay, let's try the next one. He's not gonna like it.
走着瞧吧
We'll see.
卡氏兄弟  我给你们引见一下
Castigliani brothers! Let me introduce you around.
请坐  这是达比先生  你知道的
Please take a seat. This is Mr. Darby, whom you know.
这是导演亚当•克什尔
And this is the director, Adam Kesher.
经理人罗伯特•斯密斯
And his manager, Robert Smith.
她很漂亮
She's very pretty.
先生们  想喝点什么吗?
May I offer you gentlemen anything?
蒸馏咖啡  什么都不要
Espresso. Nothing.
这相是拿来做什么的  一杯蒸馏咖啡
What's the photo for? One espresso.
就这些
No, that's it.
相信这次的咖啡你会满意的
I think you're going to enjoy your espresso this time.
我之前做过一些调查...
I've done quite a bit of research...
知道你很挑剔
knowing how hard you are to please.
这咖啡重点推荐给你试试
This one comes highly recommended.
这相是拿来做什么的?  推荐给你啊
What's the photo for? It's a recommendation.
向你推荐的  亚当
A recommendation to you, Adam.
这不是推荐  就要这个女孩
It's not a recommendation. This is the girl.
什么女孩  为什么? 这是怎么一回事  雷恩?
What girl? For what? What is this, Ray?
我们很乐意把她列为候选
We'd be happy to put her on the list for considerations.
你应该知道  许多人对这个角色有兴趣
You'd be pleased to know, there's quite a bit of interest in this role.
兴趣?  有六名顶尖的女演员争夺这个角色呢
Interest? There's six of the top actresses that want this thing.
就要这个女孩子
This is the girl.
-瑞恩  这事你来处理  -别急  亚当
-Ray, take care of this. -Hold on, hold on, Adam.
别急?
Hold on?
没门  没门
There's no way! There's no way!
餐巾
Napkin.
对不起?
Pardon?
餐巾
Napkin.
好的
Of course.
失陪
Excuse me.
还需要什么吗?
Is that all, sir?
狗屎 对不起  这可是别人重点推荐的
Shit. Sorry. That was highly recommended.
这是公认最好的蒸馏咖啡之一
That is considered one of the finest espressos in the world!
发生什么事了? 这个女孩是不可能演我的电影
What's going on here? There is no way that girl is in my movie!
-就要这女孩  -这女孩不能演我的电影
-This is the girl. -Hey, that girl is not in my film!
这电影已经不是你的了
It's no longer your film.
就要这个女孩
This is the girl.
卡氏兄弟上了那辆轿车没有?
Castigliani brothers get out of that limo?
-是那两个穿黑西服的人吗?  -是的
-The two guys in dark suits? -Yeah.
把车门开着
Yes. Leave that door open.
卡氏兄弟
Castigliani brothers?
打呀  老友
Beat it, pal.
下午好  罗科先生
Good afternoon, Mr. Roque.
她的名字叫卡米拉•罗丝
Her name is Camilla Rhodes.
导演不想要她
The director doesn't want her.
你想换掉他吗?
Do you want him replaced?
我知道他们说...
I know they said...
然后呢
Then?
然后...
Then...
那意味着我们应该...
that means we should...?
什么
Yes?
停止一切事情  就是...
Shut everything down? Is that something that...
你要我们停止一切事情吗
Do you want us to shut everything down?
那么我们会停止一切事情的
Then we'll shut everything down.
哥们  真是闻所未闻
Oh, man, that's unheard of.
真是出人意料
An accident like that, who could have foreseen that, man?
这不是真的吧?
It's unreal, right? Yeah.
难以置信
Unbelievable, man.
兄弟  瞧着挺风光的
So, bro? God, you look good.
你一直在做什么?
What have you been doing?
也就是给那家伙做点事
You know, just...doing some stuff for this guy.
是吗?  日子还过得去吗?
Are you making ends meet?
挺艰苦的
Hardly.
我知道的 看看我呆的地方
I know, man, look at my digs.
这世道真不好混  兄弟
Times are tough, bro.
没那么惨的
Hey...man, it's not that bad.
希望你别惹什么麻烦
I hope you're not gonna get in any trouble.
也就是那件事而已  你就是笑那事吧?
That was just a thing, man. That story? That made you laugh!
那故事可真逗  该死的车祸
That was a funny story, man. Fucking car accident!
嘿  那是...就是它了
Hey, so that's...that's it, huh?
那是埃德著名的黑名册
That's Ed's famous black book.in phone numbers.
以电话号码书写的世界历史
The history of the world...
我被什么东西咬了一口
Something bit me bad!
她受了重伤  可以帮忙打个电话吗?
She's hurt real bad! Could you come here and call on the phone, please?
她受了重伤  过来给医院打个电话
She's hurt real bad! You gotta come in here and call the hospital!
过来  我是说真的  我一个人应付不来
Come on, man! I'm serious about this! I can't do everything by myself!
不  放开我
不  不
姨妈  我会尽力的 那几行字我会记得滚瓜烂熟的
Aunt Ruth, I'll try. I'm gonna study those lines until I know them...
要么就在这张豪华皮沙发上
Either right here on this fabulous leather couch...
要么我会在后院 边喝咖啡边记...
or I'll take them with a coffee into the courtyard...
电影明星通常都这样
like a regular movie star.
在这见到你的朋友丽塔  真让我大吃一惊
I got a real shock to find your friend Rita here.
我进门时她正在洗澡
She was in the shower and I opened the door!
丽塔
Rita!
什么意思?
What do you mean?
她碰到了车祸
She was in an accident.
丽塔  你的朋友
Rita. Your friend.
不是的  可可开的门
No, Coco unlocked the door.
没有  可可没见到她
No, she didn't see her.
她正在睡觉
She's sleeping.
我相信这事能搞清楚的  我们不必这么做的
I'm sure there's some explanation for this. I don't think we have to do that.
别担心  姨妈  没必要报警的
Please, don't worry. Aunt Ruth, we don't need the police.
你醒了
You're awake.
我刚才搞错了
I think I misunderstood.
本来以为你跟我姨妈认识
I thought you knew my aunt and that's why you were here.
我刚和姨妈通过电话  她想让我报警
I just talked to my aunt on the phone and she wants me to call the police.
丽塔
Rita?
很抱歉  我...
I'm sorry, I...
怎么了  丽塔
What is it, Rita?
我以为睡一觉醒来...我以为睡一觉就没事了
I thought when I woke up...I thought sleep would do it.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我不知道自己是谁
I just don't know who I am.
-你是什么意思?  你叫丽塔呀 -不  我不是
-What do you mean? You're Rita. -No, I'm not.
我不知道自己的名字
I don't know what my name is.
我不知道自己是谁
I don't know who I am.
这是你的包  里面也许能找到你的名字
This is your purse. Your name must be in your purse.
你也想知道的  对吗?
You wanna know, don't you?
-是的  但...  -打开它吧
-Yes, but... -Open it.
-什么都不想要?  -不在这儿
-Sure you don't want anything? -Not here.
谢谢  喝点什么?
Thanks. A drink or something?
不  谢谢
No. Thanks, though.
有烟的话给我一根
I'll take a cigarette, if you have one.
我衬衣口袋里有
Yeah, just reach inside my shirt pocket there.
最近街上有没有新的女孩?
Any new girls on the street lately?
没有
No.
没见过
I haven't seen any.
黑头发的白人女孩?
A brunette?
可能有点蓬头垢面
Maybe a little beat-up?
没有
No.
-好好的帮我看着点  -没问题
-Keep your eyes open for me, okay? -Sure.
你保证过的
You bet you will.
这些钱...
That money...
你不知道是怎么来的吗?
you don't know where it came from?
你看到这些东西  这些钱和钥匙...
When you think of them, the money and the key...
能不能让你想起点什么来?
does it make you remember anything?
有一些...
There's something...
一些...
something...
那儿
there.
你说什么?
What did you say?
-他们把所有人都炒了  -谁把所有人都炒了?
-They fired everyone. -Who fired everyone?
是瑞恩  等等  我正在打电话
Ray did! Wait! I'm talking on the phone.
他们关闭了拍摄场  大家都走了 你最好来一下
They closed the set. Everybody's gone. You'd better get down here.
不
No.
你得跟瑞恩谈谈  这事你得搞定
You've gotta talk to Ray. You've gotta fix this.
我正要回家
I'm going home.
回家?
Home?
在办公室碰面  我们得有所动作 你得做点什么
Meet me at the office, we gotta do something. You gotta do something!
我要回家  辛西娅  亚当 听我说  这不像你的风格
I'm going home, Cynthia. Adam, this isn't like you.
拜托你到办公室来  我们肯定能做些什么的
Please, come to the office. There's gotta be something we can do!
我要回家
I'm going home.
我在想你要去哪
I wonder where you were going.
穆赫兰道
Mulholland Drive.
穆赫兰道?
Mulholland Drive?
那就是我要去的地方
That's where I was going.
穆赫兰道
Mulholland Drive.
也许车祸就发生在那
Maybe that's where the accident was.
警察局一定会有记录的 我们打个电话问问
There must be a police report. We could call.
我们到外面用公用电话打 确定下是否出过车祸
We could call anonymously just to see if there was an accident.
就像电影里的桥段 我们也像电影里的角色一样
It'll be just like in the movies! We'll pretend to be someone else.
反正我也想出去走走
I wanna walk around, anyway.
身在好莱坞  却没好好看过它呢
I'm in Hollywood and I haven't even seen any of it.
来吧  丽塔  你去吗?
Come on, Rita, do you feel up to it?
好的
Okay.
只是...
But just...
只是去搞清楚
just to see.
只是去搞清楚...
Just to see if there was an accident...
在穆赫兰道是否出过车祸
on Mulholland Drive.
洛兰尼
Lorraine?
你在家吗
You're home?
洛兰尼?
Lorraine?
现在你都看到了
Now you've done it!
忘了吧  这样比较明智
Just forget you ever saw it. It's better that way.
你到底想干什么?
What the hell are you even doing here?
你干什么?
What are you doing?
那是我的珠宝
That's my jewelry!
你这杂种  他很郁闷  洛兰尼
That bastard. You bastard! He's probably upset, Lorraine.
你干什么?
What are you doing?
住手
Stop it!
亚当  住手
Adam, stop it!
住手
Stop it!
你弄痛我了  杰里
You're hurting me! Gene!
你弄痛我了
You're hurting me!
别这么对你老婆  我就不在乎我老婆怎么做
That ain't no way to treat your wife. I don't care what she's done.
把他扔出去
Throw him out!
去你的  亚当
Damn you, Adam!
把他扔出去
Throw him out!
滚
Get out!
我们先把它藏起来
Let's hide it.
那有一个
There's one.
好莱坞警察局  我想询问一下...
Los Angeles Police Department. I'm inquiring about an accident...
昨晚在穆赫兰道上发生的车祸
last night on Mulholland Drive.
请稍等  我帮你转到交通科
I'll connect you to Traffic.
-我是白斯特警官  -我想问一下...
-Sergeant Baker. -Hi, I'm inquiring...
昨晚我听到了点声音  好像是撞车
I heard a sound last night that sounded sort of like a car crash.
穆赫兰道上是否发生了车祸?
I want to know if there was an accident on Mulholland Drive.
是的  是发生了车祸
Yes, there was.
-能告诉我出了什么事吗?  -不行
-Can you tell me what happened? -No, I can't.
-有人受伤吗?  -能告诉我你的名字吗?
-Was anyone hurt? -May I have your name, please?
是有一起车祸
There was an accident.
他不肯多说  应该就是你遇到的那起
He wouldn't tell me anything else, but that was your accident, Rita.
或许报纸上会有相关的报道
Maybe there's something about it in the papers.
来吧  我们一边喝咖啡  一边看报纸去
Come on, I'll buy you a cup of coffee and we can see.
可能发生得太晚了  今天的报纸没报道
Maybe it happened so late it's not in today's paper.
什么都没有吗?
There's nothing?
我没找到
Not that I can see.
没关系的
That's okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
戴安妮
Diane.
就这些了吗?  可以下单了吗?
Will that be all? Would you like your check?
丽塔  还要点什么吗?
Rita, you want something?
不  咖啡就行了 可以下单了
No, just...just the coffee. We'll take our check.
怎么了?  丽塔
What is it, Rita?
我想起点东西  我想起点东西
I remember something. I remember something!
想起什么了?  戴安妮•西恩
What is it? Diane Selwyn.
我好像就叫这名字
Maybe that's my name!
D•西恩  只有一个
D. Selwyn. It's the only one.
打个电话过去
I'm gonna call.
-给自己打电话很奇怪  -不一定是我
-It is strange to be calling yourself. -Maybe it's not me.
你好  是我
Hello, it's me.
请留言
Leave a message.
那不是我的声音
That's not my voice.
但我认识她
But I know her!
可能这不是戴安妮•西恩的声音  可能是你室友
Maybe that isn't Diane Selwyn's voice. Maybe that's your roommate.
如果她是戴安妮的话  应该知道你是谁
Or if it is Diane Selwyn, she could tell you who you are.
也许吧
Maybe.
也许  也许
Maybe, maybe...
亚当•克什尔?
Adam Kesher?
-亚当•克什尔?  -走开
-Adam Kesher? -Get lost!
-这是亚当•克什尔的房子  -见鬼给我滚出去
-This is Adam Kesher's house. -Like hell it is! Get out now!
滚出去
Get out!
亚当•克什尔
Adam Kesher?
滚开  他再也不会回来的了
Get out of here! He's never coming back! Ever!
估计你听不懂英语吧!
Bastard. I guess you don't understand English.
她叫你离开  门在那
She said leave. Here's the door.
杰里
Gene!
滚开
Get out!
亚当•克什尔
Adam Kesher?
-什么事?  科基  -很抱歉  克什尔先生...
-Yeah, what is it, Cookie? -I'm sorry, Mr. Kesher...
你的信用卡似乎有点问题
but there seems to be some problem with your credit cards.
什么?  我给你现金吧  科基
What? I pay you cash, Cookie.
银行的两个家伙来过这
Listen, two guys from your bank came by.
银行?
My bank?
-他们怎么知道我在这  -我不知道
-How'd they know I was here? -I don't know.
他们说了些什么?
What'd they say?
他们说你的帐户已经没钱了
They said to tell you that you're maxed out at your bank...
你的信用卡被取消了
and that your line of credit has been canceled.
真难以置信
That's unbelievable.
我...
Well, look...
我不知道发生了什么事  一群胡说八道的家伙
I don't know what's going on. That is so much baloney.
-我有大把现金  科基  -我知道 不要担心
-I got enough cash for you, Cookie. -I know, I know. Don't worry.
我很抱歉  不过我有义务提醒你...
But I'm sorry, it's my duty to inform you...
小心点 不管你躲在哪...
listen, man, whoever you're hiding from...
他们都能找到你
they know where you are.
好的
Right.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
喂
Hello?
-有人冻结了我的银行帐户 -我知道了 你在哪? 亚当
-Someone maybe shut off my money. -I know. Where are you, Adam?
-你知道了是什么意思?  -有人打电话找过你...
-Sorry, what do you mean you know? -Somebody called...
他们说你已破产了  我不信  所以我打了几个电话
they told me you were as good as broke. So I made a few calls.
-然后呢?  -你确实破产了
-And? -You're broke.
我没破产
I'm not broke!
但你确实破产了  你在哪?
I know, but you're broke. Where are you?
我在市区  科基这儿 你认识一个叫"牛仔"的人吗?
I'm at Cookie's, downtown. Do you know somebody called "The Cowboy"?
-牛仔? -是的
-"The cowboy"? -Yeah.
牛仔  这个人想见你
"The Cowboy". This guy, the Cowboy, wants to see you.
杰森觉得应该去见他
Jason said he thought it would be a good idea.
杰森认为我该去见牛仔吗?
Jason thought it would be a good idea for me to go see the Cowboy.
我是不是要带上 高顶宽边呢帽和左轮手枪?
Should I wear my 1O-gallon hat and my six-shooters?
某些迹象表明 他与所发生的事有联系
Something tells me that this guy is connected to what's happening.
亚当  你应该去见他  马上去
Adam, I think you should do it, and you should do it right away.
出了什么事?  辛西娅  真是怪异的一天
What's going on, Cynthia? It's been a very strange day.
而且越来越奇怪
And getting stranger.
我到哪和这位牛仔碰头? 要不要我骑着马去?
Where do I meet this Cowboy? Do you have to ride out to the range?
你真搞笑  如果要找他的话...
Sort of, funny boy. If I tell him the meeting's on...
到比奇伍德峡谷的顶上 那里有个围栏...
you'll go to the top of the Beachwood Canyon, there's a corral up there...
-他在那等你  -你在戏弄我?
-where he'll be. -You've gotta be kidding me.
你去不去?
Will you meet with him?
当然去
Yeah.
-今天真不是什么吉日  -什么时候?
-Sure. This has been that kind of a day. -When?
我马上致电他  然后再通知你
I'll call him right away and then I'll call you back.
如果你愿意  可以来我这里
You know, you could stay at my place, if you wanted.
-我觉得不妥  -只是让你落落脚而已
-I don't think that'd be a good idea. -I was just offering a place to stay.
非常感激  我自己会找地方的
Yes, and I appreciate the offer, Cynthia. I'll find a place.
快去给牛仔打电话  然后答复我
Just go on and give that cowboy a yodel and get on back to me.
好  我怕你什么地方可能会疏忽
Okay. But you don't know what you're missing.
别管了  小亲亲  我等你电话
Just get along, little doggie. And call me back.
大概就在这附近了  塞丽亚泊尼塔 不是很远
It's right about here. Sierra Bonita. It's not too far away.
有什么问题吗?
What's wrong with that?
我不能肯定是这儿
I'm not sure about this.
我知道你有点害怕
I know you're afraid of something.
我保证一定小心行事
We'll be careful. I promise.
等明天我们去了  就知道是不是那了
Tomorrow. We'll go over there.and we'll find out.
没事的
It'll be okay.
可能是可可
It's probably Coco.
-什么事? 需要帮忙吗?  -有人要倒霉了
-Yes, may I help you? -Someone is in trouble!
你是谁?
Who are you?
你在露茜的家里做什么?
What are you doing in Ruth's apartment?
她让我呆在这的  我是她的侄女  我叫贝蒂
She's letting me stay here. I'm her niece. My name's Betty.
不  不是的  她不是这样说的
No, it's not! That's not what she said.
有人倒霉了  大事不好了
Someone is in trouble! Something bad is happening!
抱歉我不认识你  而且...
I'm sorry, but I don't know who you are and...
露易斯  你在干什么?  露易斯
Louise? What are you doing, Louise?
我下午3点一直在找你
I've been trying to get hold of you since 3 o'clock this afternoon.
那人在我房间  她不肯走
That one is in my room and she won't leave!
我要你赶她走  马上赶她走
I want you to get her out. I want you to get her out now.
这位是露易斯•波尼尔  她没有恶意的
This is Louise Bonner. I'm sure she meant well.
露易斯  这位是贝蒂  露茜的侄女
Louise, this is Betty, this is Ruth's niece.
正好我要来看贝蒂  贝蒂是个演员
I was on my way over here to see Betty. Betty is a young actress.
我来给她送明天试镜台词
I was delivering some faxed pages of a scene for a big audition tomorrow.
-给你  甜心  -谢谢
-Well, here they are, honey. -Thank you.
走吧  露易斯  我带你回家
Come along now, Louise. I'll take you home.
-我很抱歉  这种事时有发生  -没关系
-I'm sorry. It happens sometimes. -Come on.
不  她说了有人要倒霉
No, she said it was someone else who was in trouble.
住口  我带你回家  快点
Stop it, Louise! I'm taking you home. Come on.
-晚安  贝蒂  -晚安
-Good night, Betty. -Good night.
晚安
Good night.
牛仔...
Cowboy...
您好  您好
Howdy. Howdy to you.
很美的夜晚
Beautiful evening.
谢谢你从旅馆大老远跑来见我
Thank you for coming all the way up here to see me from that nice hotel downtown.
不要紧  你想怎么样?
No problem. What's on your mind?
来了个直肠直肚的人
Well, now. Here's a man who wants to get right down to it.
很好奇  对吗?
Kind of anxious to get to it, are you?
随你怎么说吧
Whatever.
一个人的态度...
A man's attitude...
态度决定人生
a man's attitude goes some ways the way his life will be.
你同意吗?
Is that something you might agree with?
当然
Sure!
你是为了讨我欢心...
Did you answer because that's what you thought I wanted to hear...
而言不由衷...
or did you think about what I said...
还是确实这么认为的?
and answered 'cause you truly believe that to be right?
真心同意您的观点
I agree with what you said. Truly.
我的什么观点?
What'd I say?
态度很大程度上决定人生
That a man's attitude determines to a large extent how his life will be.
根据我的观点...
So since you agree...
你一定是个不在乎自己过的好不好的人
you must be a person who does not care about the good life.
怎么讲?
How's that?
停下来...
Well, stop for a little second...
反省一下吧  拜托你这么做吧
and think about it. Can you do that for me?
好的  我正在反省
Okay. I'm thinking.
你根本没在反省  你真的太自以为是了
No, you're not. You're too busy being a smart aleck to be thinking.
现在  我希望你反省  不要再自以为是了
Now, I want you to think and stop being a smart aleck.
拜托你尝试一下
Can you try that for me?
到底怎么回事?  你到底要我怎么做?
Look, where's this going? What do you want me to do?
假定有一辆双座车  一辆双座车需要几个司机?
There's sometimes a buggy. How many drivers does a buggy have?
一个
One.
假设我已经是那个唯一的司机了
So let's just say I'm driving this buggy.
如果你态度端正的话 你可以一起乘我的车
And if you fix your attitude, you can ride along with me.
我希望你明天回去上班
I want you to go back to work tomorrow.
无论如何女主角得重选  多点女孩来试镜
You were recasting the lead actress. Audition many girls for the part.
当试到那个女孩时  你得说
When you see the girl that was shown to you earlier today, you will say:
就是她了
"This is the girl."
其他角色人选仍然由你定
The rest of the cast can stay. That's up to you.
但女主角不由你定
But that lead girl is not up to you.
表现出色的话  你还能再见我一次
Now, you will see me one more time if you do good.
如果干的不好  你还会再见我两次
You'll see me two more times if you do bad.
晚安
Good night.
-你还没走  -我又回来了  这不正如你所愿吗?
-You're still here? -I thought that's what you wanted.
-没人想看见你  -真的吗?
-Nobody wants you here! -Really?
我父母就在楼上  他们以为你已经走了
My parents are right upstairs. They think you've left!
-那又怎样?  -很吃惊了 我要叫他们下来 叫我爸下来
-So? -Surprise. I can call them. I can call my dad.
你不会的  你威胁我是没有用的
But you won't. If you're trying to blackmail me...
你玩的游戏很危险
it's not going to work! You're playing a dangerous game here.
你知道我想怎么样的  也不是很难满足的
You know what I want. It's not that difficult.
出去  否则我把父亲叫下来
Get out! Get out before I call my dad!
他很信任你  把你当最好的朋友
He trusts you! You're his best friend.
一切都将结束
This will be the end of everything.
你呢?  你父亲会怎么看你?
What about you? What will your dad think about you?
不要说了  你一开始就这样说
Stop! Just stop it! That's what you said from the beginning.
如果我把实情告诉他们  你就要去坐牢了
If I tell what happened, they'll arrest you and put you in jail.
请马上离开这  免得我...
Get out of here before...
免得你什么?  免得...
Before what? Before...
-我宰了你  -那坐牢的就是你了
-I kill you. -Then they'd put you in jail.
然后我会哭啊哭  接着很动情地说...
Then I cry, cry, cry, and then I say with big emotion...
我恨你  我恨我们俩个
"I hate you! I hate us both!"
好蹩脚的剧本  不过你真的很棒
Such a lame scene. But you are really good.
谢谢你  亲爱的
Thank you, darling.
你是谁?
Hi, there. Who are you?
贝蒂
Betty?
贝蒂  能到外面聊几句吗?
Betty, can I see you outside for a minute?
什么事?  可可
What is it, Coco?
你姨妈打电话给我
Your aunt called.
我就担心会这样
I was afraid of that.
她想弄清楚  到底是谁在她家里
She wants to know who's staying in her apartment.
她不过呆一两个晚上就会走的
It's just for a night or two. Until she finds her own place.
我向姨妈解释过的  但当时飞机正在起飞
I tried to explain that to aunt Ruth but the connection was bad...
电话线路不是很好  她可能有点误会
and her plane was leaving, and she got it all mixed up.
我说过这是我的朋友丽塔...
I kept telling her that it was my friend Rita...
可她说不认识什么丽塔
and she kept saying she didn't know any Ritas.
看着我  甜心  她人很好的
Look at me straight, sweetie. Coco, she's very nice.
甜心  你是个好孩子...
Honey, you're a good kid...
你的话听起来不错...
but what you're telling me is a load of horse puckey.
但我却总觉的不是很踏实
Even though it comes from a good place.
不过  我相信你会处理好这事的
I'm gonna trust you to sort this thing out.
-谢谢  -别让我失望
-Thank you. -Don't make me out to be a sucker.
露易斯•波尼尔说过这里要出事  记得吗? 就是昨晚
Louise Bonner said there is trouble in there, remember last night?
她说的不一定对...
Well, sometimes she's wrong...
但如果真有什么麻烦  就得马上解决掉
but if there is trouble, get rid of it.
没事吧?
Is everything all right?
-我在这给你添麻烦了吧  -没  一切都挺好的
-Is it bad for you that I'm here? -No, no, everything is A-Okay.
我去把三文治弄好  还有一个小时就要试镜了
Now, I've gotta fix that sandwich. And my audition is in one hour!
两小时后应该能回来
I hope I'm back in a couple of hours.
-别把可乐都喝光了 -祝你好运
-And don't drink all the Coke. -Good luck.
等我回来后会叫车在外面等着  你准备好
When I get back, I'll keep the cab waiting, so be ready to go.
贝蒂•艾姆斯  给你介绍一下...
Betty Elms, I would like you to meet...
杰克•土特曼  我的助手
Jack Tutman, my assistant.
伍迪•卡特滋 他会和
Woody Katz, who we have cast in the part of Chuck...
你一起表演
and will do the scene with you.
鲍勃•保波克  我们的导演
Bob Rooker, our director...
还有朱丽叶•卡文迪
and Julie Chadwick.
以及让人惊喜的嘉宾  里尼•詹姆斯
Now, our surprise guest, Lynne James.
唉  我们请不起她演戏
Alas, we can't afford her to cast our show but...
不过挑选演员  她也是最有眼光的
well, as casting agents go, she is the best.
谢谢  沃里  你好  贝蒂
Why, thank you, Wally. Hello, Betty.
幸会  这是我的助手  尼奇
Very pleased to meet you. This is my assistant, Nikki.
还有可爱的马莎•约翰逊  以前你见过的
And the ever lovely Martha. Martha Johnson, whom you met out front.
你好
Hi.
可以开始了吗?
So, shall we give it a go?
要不要先来杯水或是咖啡?
Would you like a water, a coffee before we begin?
不要了
No, I'm fine.
好的  那么大家各就各位
Well then, let's everyone take a seat.
贝蒂  到伍迪那边去  准备开始了
Betty, why don't you join Woody over there and we'll play the scene.
鲍勃  有什么要交待贝蒂的?
Bob, do you have anything you wish to say? Something to Betty before we begin?
注意  两个人之间的不是争论
No. It's not a contest. The two of them. with themselves.
所以不要试图去演...
So don't play it for real...
要自然一点
until it gets real.
好的
Okay.
告诉我哪受伤了  宝贝
Just tell me where it hurts, baby.
什么?
What?
我看应该演得亲热点 就像和其他女孩试镜一样
I wanna play this one nice and close like we did with that other girl...
黑头发那个叫什么名字?   感觉挺好的 你认为怎样
what's her name? With the black hair. It felt good, what do you think?
很好  伍迪 说那句台词别太快了
That's good, Woody. Just don't rush that line again. I told you...
你说的是那句台词吧?  "免得什么?"
the line where you say: "Before what?"
演戏是相互影响的 我只是配合而已  她们都说的很快
Bobby, acting is reacting. I just play off them. They all say:
"他们会逮捕你"  或者"你会去坐牢" 都说的很快
"They're gonna arrest you", like that, and: "They'll put you in jail."
她们说的很快  我也自然说得快
They say it the same way. So when they say it, I just react.
-你叫什么名字?  -贝蒂
-What's your name? -Betty.
听着  如果你能慢一点 我也会慢一点的  好吗?
Betty, look. You don't rush it, I don't rush it, okay?
我们亲热一点  就像是在电影里  好吗?
Now, we're gonna play this nice and close just like in the movies, okay?
父亲最好的朋友上班去了
Dad's best friend goes to work.
鲍勃?
Bob?
开始
action!
你还没走
You're still here.
我回来了
I came back.
-这不正如你所愿吗?  -没人想看见你
-I thought that's what you wanted. -Nobody wants you here.
真的吗?
Really?
我父母就在楼上  他们以为你已经走了
My parents are right upstairs. They think you've left.
那又怎样?很惊讶吧
So, surprise!
-我要叫他们下来  我要叫我父亲下来  -你不会的
-I can call them, I can call my dad. -But you won't.
你会玩死自己的
You're playing a dangerous game here.
你恐吓我是没有用的
If you're trying to blackmail me...
你知道我想怎么样的
it's not gonna work.
也不是很难满足的
You know what I want. It's not that difficult.
出去
Get out.
要不我把父亲叫下来
Get out before I call my dad.
他很信任你  把你当最好的朋友
He trusts you. You're his.best friend.
一切都将结束
This will be the end of everything.
你呢?  你父亲会怎么看你?
What about you? What'll your dad think about you?
别说了
Stop it.
你从一开始就这么说
That's what you said from the beginning.
如果我把实情告诉他们 他们会把你送进监狱
If I tell them what happened, they will arrest you and put you in jail.
请马上离开这
So get out of here...
免得我...
before...
免得你什么?
Before what?
免得...
Before...
我宰了你
I kill you.
那你就要去坐牢了
Well, then they'd put you in jail.
我恨你
I hate you.
我恨我们俩个
I hate us both.
我要把她带到那边  演的很好
I'm gonna take her over there. Yeah, big time.
就是这样了
Well, there it was.
对  就这样  不错 宝贝  你演戏挺有一套
Yeah, there it was, all right. Baby, you got a way with you. Really.
鲍勃?
Bob?
真的很好
Very good. Really.
略有点造作 不过还是挺动情的
I mean, it was forced maybe, but still humanistic.
是的  非常好
Very good. Really!
真的
Really.
谢谢  贝蒂  我是真心的
Oh, I thank you, Betty. And I really mean that, sincerely.
我是说...
I mean, it was...
太优秀了
extraordinary.
你的姨妈会为你骄傲的
You've done your aunt proud today.
一有机会我就会告诉她
I'm going to tell her that first chance I get.
现在  你和我 很快又要谈谈了
Now, you and I are going to speak again very soon.
谢谢  布朗先生
Thank you, Mr. Brown. Thank you, Wally.
你们肯定有不少话要谈  我们带贝蒂出去了
I'm sure you all have a lot to talk about. We'll walk Betty out.
你能来是我们的荣幸  里尼
Yes, indeed. And it was our pleasure, Lynne.
别把自己当外人  我们很高兴你能来
Don't you be a stranger around here. We'd love to have you here.
走吧  贝蒂  再次感谢  布朗先生
Come on, Betty. Thank you again, Mr. Brown.
很高兴见到大家
And it was nice meeting all of you.
再见
Bye.
Bye!
她真是太棒了  你究竟是从哪发掘她的?
She's a slam-dunk! Where the hell did you find her?
天哪  真的太烂了
God, that was awful!
不是说你 你演技一流  但可怜的沃里
Not you, Betty. You were stellar, and I mean that. But poor Wally.
他永远演不好戏  他已经是20年前的人物了
He'll never get that picture made. Wally's days were up 2O years ago.
伍迪•卡特滋做这些只是兴趣
You know Woody Katz is only doing it for a favor.
至于演技  我听说非常烂
And the cast they have so far is terrible.
是的  很烂  沃里这个可怜的蠢老头
Oh, God, terrible! That poor old fool Wally.
他很好  他看起来很和蔼
He was very nice and he seems so sweet.
而且沃里...布朗先生是我姨妈的密友
And Wally...Mr. Brown is a very close friend of my aunt's.
别误会了  我爱沃里
Don't get me wrong, I love Wally.
本应如此  我和他结婚10年了
I ought to, I was married to him for 1O years.
我喜欢演员  所有的演员 我们只是有点油罢了
And I love actors. All actors. We just get a little catty sometimes.
我们给你介绍一位出类拔萃的导演
We want to take you across and introduce you to a director who's a head above the rest.
他那部电影很适合你
He's got a project you will kill for.
一炮而红
Knock right out of the park!
停  非常感谢  卡罗  我很快就回来
Cut it! Thank you very much, Carol. Checking the gate?
谢谢  我们会给你个结果的
Checking the gate! Thank you. We'll tell you what happens next!
非常感谢你的光临  我知道你很忙
Thank you very much for coming in. I know how busy you are.
和我开玩笑? 我喜欢这个剧本  告诉我在哪签字
Are you kidding me? I loved the script. Just show me where to sign.
我喜欢你  不过我要见完...
I love you, but there's no way they're gonna let me cast this thing...
所有人选后再决定  我会尽快通知你的
until I've seen everyone. I'll let you know as soon as I can.
我知道你会的  因为我的经纪人会日夜骚扰你 我也会
I know you will. Because my manager is gonna be bugging you. And me!
这是我的荣幸  离开这儿  你对我太冷谈了
My pleasure. Now get outta here. You're so cruel to me.
我演定了这角色  再会
I'm the girl who's playing this part. I'll see you later.
汉克  汉克在哪
Hank? Where's Hank?
-下一位是谁  汉克  -是卡米拉•罗丝
-Who's next, Hank? -Camilla Rhodes.
-她准备好了吗?  -都准备好了
-Is she ready? -All ready.
-带她进来  -下一位卡米拉•罗丝
-Bring her in. -Camilla Rhodes, next.
西尔维亚诺兹故事  卡米拉•罗丝
"Sylvia North Story". Camilla Rhodes, take one.
好了  开始了
Okay, here we go. Let's lock it up, please.
请放音乐
Roll sound, please. That's fit.
开始
Playback and action.
叫杰森来这  辛迪  亚当想见杰森
Get Jason over here. Cindy, Adam wants to see Jason.
怎么没有告诉我  你有事找我吗?
Why haven't you told me? Did you want to tell something?
就是这个女孩了
This is the girl.
真有眼光  亚当
Excellent choice, Adam.
天啊
Oh, my goodness.
我得走了
I have to be somewhere.
我约了朋友
I promised a friend.
对不起  我得走了  现在?
I'm sorry, I must go. Now?
应该就在这附近了
Should be around here.
2-5-9-0  就是它了
259O. That's it.
在那边  眼熟吗?
Up there! Does it look familiar?
-别停车  -怎么了?  你看到什么了?
-Don't stop! -What is it? What do you see?
坐在那辆车前面的人 你认识他们吗?
Those men, in front, in the car. Do you know them?
绕到他们后面去
Keep going. Go around to the back.
西恩  12号
Selwyn, number 12.
你吓死我了
Now you got me scared.
看到没?
You see?
都说过没什么可怕的了
I told you there was nothing to be afraid of.
贝蒂  等等
Betty, wait. Wait!
别
Don't.
没人在家
No one's home.
什么事?
Yes?
戴安妮
Diane?
她在17号
Number 17.
但那上面写着是12号
But it said number 12.
我和她换了房子  她在17号
I switched apartments with her.
在左边的最尽头
She's in 17. It's down at the end, on the left.
不过她好几天没露面了
But she hasn't been around for a few days.
我们可以给她留个条
We'll leave her a note.
我和你们一起去
I'll go with you.
我还有东西在她那里
She still got some of my stuff.
你们去吧  我要接个电话
You go ahead. I gotta get that.
-估计你不是戴安妮•西恩  -我也觉得不是
-Guess you're not Diane Selwyn. -Guess I'm not.
可能还是没人在家
There's still no one home, I guess.
你在干什么?  来吧  帮我一把
What are you doing? Come on, help me in.
我要把前门打开
Come on, I'll open the front door.
别
No!
帮帮我
Come on.
Come on!
我知道你在做什么
I know what you're doing.
我知道你要做什么
I know what you have to do.
还是让我来吧
But let me do it.
让我来吧
Let me do it.
看着已经不像你了
You look like someone else.
晚安  贝蒂
Good night, Betty.
在屋里你不需要戴的
You don't have to wear that in the house.
什么?
What?
假发
The wig!
只是想多看会现在的样子  睡觉时我会脱下的
I was just looking at myself again. I'll take it off to sleep.
别睡在沙发上了
You don't have to sleep on that couch.
-没关系的  -不要  这张床大的很
-No, it's okay.- No, it's not. This is a huge bed.
来吧  上来睡个好觉吧
Come on, just get in and get a good night sleep.
比睡沙发舒服多了  是吗?
It's more comfortable than the couch, isn't it?
谢谢你  贝蒂
Thank you, Betty.
别客气  昨晚不该让你睡沙发的
It's nothing. I shouldn't have let you sleep on the couch last night.
不  我是指...
No, I mean...
谢谢你所做的一切
thank you for everything.
你太客气了
You're welcome.
晚安  亲爱的贝蒂
Good night, sweet Betty.
晚安
Good night.
你以前这么做过吗?
Have you ever done this before?
我不知道
I don't know.
你呢?
Have you?
我想和你在一起
I want to with you.
我爱你
I'm in love with you.
寂静
Silence.
没有乐队
There's no band.
There's no orchestra.
寂静
Silence!
丽塔  没有乐队
Rita? There's no band.
丽塔  醒醒
Rita, wake up!
没事的  没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
不  不对
No, it's not okay.
怎么?
What's wrong?
跟我到一个地方去
Go with me somewhere.
现在是2点  凌晨2点
It's two o'clock. It's two o'clock in the morning.
跟我到一个地方去
Go with me somewhere.
可以
Sure.
现在吗?
Now?
马上就去
Right now.
没有乐队
There's no band!
There is no band!
这全是...
This is all...
这些全是录音
a tape recording.
没有乐队  然而...
There's no band, and yet...
我们可以听到乐声
we hear a band.
如果我们想听竖笛...
If we want to hear a clarinet...
听着...
listen...
请听长号声
A muted trombone.
减弱的喇叭声
A muted trumpet.
这全是录音
It's all recorded.
没有乐队
There's no band!
这全是...
It is all...
一盒录音带
a tape.
这全是...幻觉
It is an illusion.
听着
Listen!
女士们  先生们  欢迎光临寂静酒吧
Ladies and gentlemen, let Club Silencio introduce to you...
下面丽贝卡•德•瑞为我们演唱
"La Llorona de Los Angeles". Rebekah del Rio.
贝蒂
Betty?
你在哪?
Where are you?
嘿  靓女
Hey, pretty girl.
该起床了
Time to wake up.
你去哪了? 你要干嘛?
Where have you been? What do you want?
来拿我的灯和盘子
My lamp and dishes.
戴安妮  已经三个星期了
Come on, Diane, it's been three weeks.
盘子放到那个箱子里了
I put your dishes in that box.
那是我的烟灰缸  拿走吧
That's my ashtray. Take it.
我只是想确认一下  戴安妮
Anytime. I'm just making sure, Diane.
就这些了吗?
This is it?
顺便说一下  那两个探员又来找过你
By the way, those two detectives came by again looking for you.
卡米拉
Camilla!
你终于回来了
You've come back.
刚才你说什么?  美人
What was that you were saying, beautiful?
我说...
I said...
你令我疯狂
you drive me wild.
我们不该再这样做
We shouldn't do this anymore.
不要这样说
Don't say that.
永远不要这样说
Don't ever say that.
不要  戴安妮
Don't, Diane!
住手
Stop it!
戴安妮  住手
Diane, stop!
我以前已经跟你说过
I've tried to tell you this before.
因为他  对吗?
It's him, isn't it?
我不是教怎么演这出戏  你只需要...
I'm not trying to show you how to do the scene, but just...
看着我做  相信你会明白我的意思
watch me and I think you'll understand what I'm getting at.
不要坐得那么拘谨
Don't sit so rigid, just...
放松
just relax.
现在是二人世界  非常的惬意
Now, the two of you are alone and it's real comfortable.
就像你们以前认识
Like you've known each other forever.
即使什么也不说也很惬意
Even if you don't say anything, it's real comfortable.
汉克  可以清一下场吗? 这里太多人了
Hank, can you just clear the set? There's too many people around here.
让我们把这演完  请清场
Let's get this worked out. Clear the set!
大家都喝咖啡去
Everyone have a cup of coffee.
请! 戴安妮可以留下吗?
Everyone, please! Can Diane stay?
当然可以  汉克  让戴安妮留下
Yeah, sure, Diane can stay. Hank, let Diane stay!
戴安妮
Diane!
当她开始哭的时候 不要拉她过来
Now, when she starts to cry, don't pull her towards you.
让她自己靠过来 让她靠过来
Let her fall into you. Just let her fall.
你吻她是个连贯的动作
And when you kiss her...it's just a continuation of that move.
中间是没有停顿的
There's no break.
熄灯
Kill the lights!
别发癫了 不要这样
Don't be mad. Don't make it be like this.
你想让我视而不见吗?
Oh, sure, you want me to make this easy for you.
没门  不会的
No fucking way! It's not gonna be!
我可不是好糊弄的 戴安妮
It's not easy for me! Diane!
喂  是我 请留言
Hello, it's me. Leave a message.
戴安妮?
Diane?
喂 戴安妮?
Hello? Diane?
卡米拉
Camilla.
戴安妮  车正在等着  你没事吧?
Diane, the car's waiting. Are you okay?
你来吗?
You coming?
好的  这对我来说太有意义了
Good. It means so much to me.
快点吧  车就在你门外等着
Go on. The car's right outside your house.
一直在等你  知道吗?
It's been waiting, okay?
好的
Okay.
穆赫兰道6980号
It's 698O, Mulholland Drive.
穆赫兰道
Mulholland Drive.
你要做什么?  我们不是在这停的呀!
What are you doing? We don't stop here.
让你惊喜一下
A surprise.
捷径
Shortcut.
来吧  甜心
Come on, sweetheart.
很美
It's beautiful.
一条秘道
A secret path.
时间正好
Perfect timing.
欢迎你  戴安妮
Welcome, Diane.
那么...为爱干杯
Well...Here's to love.
为爱干杯
Here's to love.
她来了
Here she is!
你没见过我母亲吧
I don't believe you met my mother.
嗨  我是戴安妮•西恩
Hi. I'm Diane Selwyn.
叫我可可就行了  大家都这样叫我
Just call me Coco, everybody does. Pleased to meet you.
幸会  去吃东西吧  我饿了
Well, let's eat! I'm starving!
抱歉我迟到了
I'm sorry I was late.
我来自安大略的深湖镇
I'm from Deep River, Ontario.
一个小镇 你从加拿大远道而来
A small town. So you rolled in here from Canada.
我一直想来这里
I always wanted to come here.
因为一场吉特巴舞比赛的胜利
I won this jitterbug contest.
让我有了演戏的欲望
That sort of led to acting.
你知道  是想演戏
You know, wanting to act.
我姨妈死的时候...
When my aunt died...
留了些钱给我
Anyway, she left me some money.
-她在这工作过  -和电影有关吗?
-She worked here. -In the movies?
是的
Yes.
你怎么认识卡米拉的?
How did you meet Camilla?
通过"西尔维亚诺兹故事"  卡米拉演的很好
On the "Sylvia North Story". Camilla was great in that.
我从没和卢姬去过卡萨布兰卡
I never went to Casablanca with Luigi.
真可惜  那就去呀
What a pity! Then go!
我是很想做女主角
I wanted the lead so bad.
不过卡米拉得到了这个角色
Anyway, Camilla got the part.
导演...
The director...
鲍勃•保波克
Bob Rooker?
是的
Yes.
他没怎么考虑过我
He didn't think so much of me.
总之我们就在那时成为朋友的
Anyway, that's when we became friends.
她帮过我...
She helped me...
让我在她的电影里演一些角色
getting some parts in some of her films.
我明白
I see.
因此我有物资  她有人才
So I got the pool, and she got the pool man.
简直不能相信  我想给法官买一辆劳斯莱斯
I couldn't believe it. I wanted to buy that judge a Rolls Royce.
有时奇迹会出现
Sometimes, good things happen.
最精彩的总是留到最后
So I guess we've saved the best for last.
-你来和大家说吧  -不  还是你来吧
-Do you want to tell them? -No, you tell them.
卡米拉和我...
Camilla and I...
准备...
are going to be...
不好意思
Sorry about that.
我不要了
No, I'm fine.
就是这个女孩了
This is the girl.
别在这给我看
Don't show me this fucking thing here.
不过是张明星照  人人都可以有的
It's just an actress' photo resume. Everybody's got one.
带钱了吗?
You got the money?
当然
I sure do.
好的  把钱给我  我们就算成交了
Okay, now, once you hand that over to me, it's a done deal.
你真想这么做吗?
You sure you want this?
做梦都想
More than anything in this world.
事成后  你会在我告诉你的地方找到这个
When it's finished, you'll find this where I told you.
用来开什么的?
What's it open?
寂静